{
  "data": [
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "001",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberJS",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What is Ember.JS?",
        "correct-answer": "An open-source JavaScript web framework.",
        "options": [
          "An open-source JavaScript web framework.",
          "A small piece of burning or glowing coal or wood in a dying fire.",
          "A programming language.",
          "A temperature mug."
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "002",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberJS",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "score": false,
        "question": "Ember consists of five key concepts. What are they?",
        "correct-answer": "Routes, Models, Templates, Components, Services",
        "options": [
          "JavaScript, Models, Templates, Components, Services",
          "JavaScript, Routes, Templates, Components, Services",
          "Routes, Models, Templates, Components, Services",
          "JavaScript, Routes, Templates, Components, DOM"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "003",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberJS",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What are Templates (Handlebars)?",
        "correct-answer": "Builds the application's HTML into DOM elements",
        "options": [
          "Its just HTML",
          "Builds the application's HTML into DOM elements",
          "Another programming language",
          "Designs which Ember gives to developers to create beautiful web pages."
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "004",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberJS",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "Why is Ember like Ruby on Rails?",
        "correct-answer": "Ember follows the 'Convention over Configuration' and 'Don't Repeat Yourself' principles.",
        "options": [
          "There is Ruby used in Ember.",
          "The founder of Ruby on Rails is also the founder of Ember.",
          "Ember follows the 'Convention over Configuration' and 'Don't Repeat Yourself' principles.",
          "Ember and Ruby on Rails are easy to learn frameworks."
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "005",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberJS",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "Who are some companies that have endorsed Ember.JS?",
        "correct-answer": "LinkedIn, Apple Music, Square",
        "options": [
          "Facebook, Chipotle, LinkedIn",
          "Facebook, Square, Google",
          "LinkedIn, Apple Music, Google",
          "LinkedIn, Apple Music, Square"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "006",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberJS",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What is the difference between a Classic Component and a Glimmer Component?",
        "correct-answer": "If a component template doesn't have a related JavaScript file.",
        "options": [
          "The only difference is the syntax.",
          "There is no difference...",
          "If the component looks shiney and new.",
          "If a component template doesn't have a related JavaScript file."
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "007",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberJS",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What is Liquid Fire?",
        "correct-answer": "Provides animation support for Ember applications.",
        "options": [
          "The name of Ember's Development Team.",
          "Ember's version of git.",
          "Ember's online education forum.",
          "Provides animation support for Ember applications."
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "008",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberJS",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "score": false,
        "question": "Who Founded Ember.JS?",
        "correct-answer": "Yehuda Katz",
        "options": ["Steve Jobs", "Yehuda Katz", "Bill Gates", "Janese Swanson"]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "009",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberJS",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What does the concept 'stability without stagnation' mean?",
        "correct-answer": "Backwards compatibility is important and can be maintained while still innovating and evolving the framework.",
        "options": [
          "Backwards compatibility is important and can be maintained while still innovating and evolving the framework.",
          "Ember wants to move forward as fast as possible and be the best framework out there.",
          "Backwards compatibility isn't very important.",
          "The only thing that matters to Ember is backward compatibility."
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "010",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberCLI",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "score": false,
        "question": "How do you start the build of an Ember app in the command line?",
        "correct-answer": "$. ember serve",
        "options": [
          "$. ember play",
          "$. ember serve",
          "$. ember start",
          "$. ember go"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "011",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberCLI",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What is EmberCLI used for?",
        "correct-answer": "Its used to create, build, serve, and test Ember.js apps and addons.",
        "options": [
          "EmberCLI doesn't exist, but will in the future.",
          "Its used to navigate though Ember apps",
          "Its used to create, build, serve, and test Ember.js apps and addons.",
          "You must write all your code with EmberCLI."
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "012",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberCLI",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "score": false,
        "question": "EmberCLI's development server comes with a live reload.",
        "correct-answer": "True",
        "options": ["True", "False"]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "013",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberCLI",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What build tool is used when running an Ember App?",
        "correct-answer": "Broccoli",
        "options": ["Babel", "NPM", "Cucumber", "Broccoli"]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "014",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberCLI",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What is the default port used in the browser when the pipeline is built?",
        "correct-answer": "4200",
        "options": ["900", "6000", "4200", "4900"]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "015",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberCLI",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What is a blueprint in EmberCLI",
        "correct-answer": "Code generators for creating models, controllers, and components.",
        "options": [
          "Code generators for creating models, controllers, and components.",
          "Code generators for creating custom files.",
          "Creates, organizes, and maintains the application file structure.",
          "All of the above"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "016",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberCLI",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "score": false,
        "question": "What does the command '$. ember t -f' do?",
        "correct-answer": "It will run only the tests with a description that matches a phrase.",
        "options": [
          "It will run only the unit test module for a utility by `name`, on every change.",
          "It will run your tests on every file-change.",
          "It will run only the tests with a description that matches a phrase.",
          "It will run your test-suite in your current shell once."
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "017",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberCLI",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "score": false,
        "question": "EmberCLIâ€™s runtime is configurable via a file named .ember-cli. What can be configured here?",
        "correct-answer": "",
        "options": ["CSS configurations.", "blah", "blah", "All of the above."]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "018",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberCLI",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah blah",
        "correct-answer": "",
        "options": ["blah blah", "blah", "blah", "blah"]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "019",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberDATA",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah",
        "correct-answer": "blah",
        "options": [
          "blah",
          "blah blah",
          "blah blah blah",
          "blah blah blah blah"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "020",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberDATA",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah",
        "correct-answer": "blah",
        "options": [
          "blah",
          "blah blah",
          "blah blah blah",
          "blah blah blah blah"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "021",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberDATA",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah",
        "correct-answer": "blah",
        "options": [
          "blah",
          "blah blah",
          "blah blah blah",
          "blah blah blah blah"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "022",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberDATA",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah",
        "correct-answer": "blah",
        "options": [
          "blah",
          "blah blah",
          "blah blah blah",
          "blah blah blah blah"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "023",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberDATA",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah",
        "correct-answer": "blah",
        "options": [
          "blah",
          "blah blah",
          "blah blah blah",
          "blah blah blah blah"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "024",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberDATA",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah",
        "correct-answer": "blah",
        "options": [
          "blah",
          "blah blah",
          "blah blah blah",
          "blah blah blah blah"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "025",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberDATA",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah",
        "correct-answer": "blah",
        "options": [
          "blah",
          "blah blah",
          "blah blah blah",
          "blah blah blah blah"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "026",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberDATA",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah",
        "correct-answer": "blah",
        "options": [
          "blah",
          "blah blah",
          "blah blah blah",
          "blah blah blah blah"
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "questions",
      "id": "027",
      "attributes": {
        "category": "EmberDATA",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "score": false,
        "question": "blah",
        "correct-answer": "blah",
        "options": [
          "blah",
          "blah blah",
          "blah blah blah",
          "blah blah blah blah"
        ]
      }
    }
  ]
}
